easyvisitors.com 2016-05-28

# PRIVACY POLICY | Easy Visitors

We take the privacy of our customers very seriously. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.

**How we collect information**  
We may collect personally identifiable information from users in a variety of ways, including through online forms for ordering products and services, and other instances where users are invited to volunteer such information. We may also collect information about how users use our website, for example, by tracking the number views received by the pages of the website or the domains from which users originate. We may use cookies to track how users use our website. A cookie is a piece of software that a web server can store on the users computer and use to identify the user should they visit the website again. While not all of the information that we collect from users is personally identifiable, it may be associated with personally identifiable information that users provide us through our Web site.

**How we use information**  
We may use personally identifiable information collected through our website to contact users regarding products and services offered by Visitor Jump and otherwise to enhance users experience. We may also use information collected through our website for research regarding the effectiveness of the website and the marketing, advertising and sales efforts of our business.

**Disclosure of information**  
We will never disclose information collected from users to third parties. However, we may disclose aggregate, anonymous data based on information collected from users to investors and potential partners. Finally, we may transfer information collected from users in connection with a sale of our business.

**Questions**  
If you have any questions regarding this privacy policy, please feel free to contact us.
